[
  {
    "id": "T6D01",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following devices or circuits changes an alternating current into a varying direct current signal?",
    "answers": [
      "Transformer",
      "Rectifier",
      "Amplifier",
      "Reflector"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D02",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is a relay?",
    "answers": [
      "An electrically-controlled switch",
      "A current controlled amplifier",
      "An inverting amplifier",
      "A pass transistor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D03",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following is a reason to use shielded wire?",
    "answers": [
      "To decrease the resistance of DC power connections",
      "To increase the current carrying capability of the wire",
      "To prevent coupling of unwanted signals to or from the wire",
      "To couple the wire to other signals"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D04",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following displays an electrical quantity as a numeric value?",
    "answers": [
      "Potentiometer",
      "Transistor",
      "Meter",
      "Relay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D05",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What type of circuit controls the amount of voltage from a power supply?",
    "answers": [
      "Regulator",
      "Oscillator",
      "Filter",
      "Phase inverter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D06",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What component changes 120 V AC power to a lower AC voltage for other uses?",
    "answers": [
      "Variable capacitor",
      "Transformer",
      "Transistor",
      "Diode"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D07",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which of the following is commonly used as a visual indicator?",
    "answers": [
      "LED",
      "FET",
      "Zener diode",
      "Bipolar transistor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D08",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following is combined with an inductor to make a resonant circuit?",
    "answers": [
      "Resistor",
      "Zener diode",
      "Potentiometer",
      "Capacitor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D09",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What is the name of a device that combines several semiconductors and other components into one package?",
    "answers": [
      "Transducer",
      "Multi-pole relay",
      "Integrated circuit",
      "Transformer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D10",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What is the function of component 2 in figure T-1?",
    "answers": [
      "Give off light when current flows through it",
      "Supply electrical energy",
      "Control the flow of current",
      "Convert electrical energy into radio waves"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6D11",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which of the following is a resonant or tuned circuit?",
    "answers": [
      "An inductor and a capacitor in series or parallel",
      "A linear voltage regulator",
      "A resistor circuit used for reducing standing wave ratio",
      "A circuit designed to provide high-fidelity audio"
    ]
  }
]